http://www.diabetesincontrol.com/privacy-policy/

Overview
The owner of this website, HIPER LLC (HIPER) is committed to protecting the privacy of our users (referred to as either “you” or “Users”). HIPER uses its best efforts to ensure that the information you submit directly to HIPER remains private and is used only for the purposes as set forth herein.
Applicability of Policy
This Privacy Statement applies only to information collected from you or submitted by you on the HIPER website, where the information is submitted directly to HIPER. The policy is not applicable to HIPER partner websites. Each participating HIPER partner website may have its own privacy policy, which we encourage you to read and understand. HIPER has no authority over any partner website’s individual privacy policy.
General Information Collected
First and foremost, HIPER does not automatically obtain any personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, phone number, or email address, when you visit our website unless you voluntarily provide such information. HIPER may, however, automatically collect non-personally identifiable information about you, such as the server your computer is logged onto, your browser type (for example, Firefox or Internet Explorer), and the Web pages you visited. This non-personally identifiable information collected by HIPER is used for the purpose of improving the HIPER website to make it more useful to you.
User Specific Information Collection
HIPER occasionally asks for personal information to fulfill your requests for contact or more information. Whenever HIPER asks for such personally identifiable information (e.g., name, address, email address, etc.), we will clearly disclose what information is required, what information is optional, and how that information may be used.
Limitations on Disclosures
Personally identifiable information in the HIPER database will not be sold or disclosed to any merchant, advertiser or Web publisher. However, HIPER does disclose aggregate information, which does not identify individuals or any personally identifiable information, to business partners, advertisers and other third parties. HIPER also reserves the right to use such non-personally identifiable information gathered on the HIPER website for promoting HIPER products and services.
Cookies
HIPER, along with thousands of other websites, uses cookies to enhance your Web-viewing experience. Cookies are small files that your Web browser places on your computer’s hard drive to collect information about you. HIPER cookies do not damage your system or files in any way. Cookies work as follows: When you log on to the HIPER website, HIPER assigns you a unique number and records that number in the cookie file of your computer. Then, when you visit again, HIPER reads this number to help gain information about your use of our website. The HIPER cookie will not be associated with any personal information about you, and HIPER will not be able to identify you personally online.
While we believe that cookies enhance your Web experience with HIPER, you have the option of setting your Web browser to reject cookies. However, doing so may negatively impact the performance of the website.
Our Advertising Partner
Our advertising partner eHealthcare Solutions may collect and store certain information automatically when you visit our website. eHealthcare Solutions may collect certain personally identifiable information you voluntarily submit on our website or on other websites who partner with eHealthcare Solutions. eHealthcare Solutions may also automatically collect and store information when you view advertisements that appear on our website. Your personally identifiable information may be used to verify the accuracy of the information you submit, and all information collected (personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable) may be used for marketing purposes, to deliver more relevant advertising and content, and to improve your overall experience at this website. Please review the eHealthcare Solutions Privacy Policy to obtain more about how this information is utilized. You can opt out of targeting based on your personal information or non-personally identifiable information (i.e., cookies, pixel tags, clear gifs and/or similar devices) gathered on this and other Network sites by clicking here, visiting the preference site and following the instructions.
Child Privacy
HIPER does not specifically or intentionally collect information about children. If you are concerned about your child’s use of the websites, you may use Web filtering technology to supervise and limit access to websites.
Changes to Privacy Statement
This Privacy Statement may be updated from time to time. Changes to this Privacy Statement will be posted by HIPER on its website. It is your obligation to review this Privacy Statement from time to time, and your continued use of the HIPER website after changes have been posted will be deemed to be your acceptance of the revised Statement. If at any time you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Statement, you may contact HIPER via email at info@EHSmail.com.
Security
HIPER will maintain the confidentiality of the information that it collects during your visit to the HIPER website. HIPER maintains internal practices that help to protect the security and confidentiality of this information by limiting employee access to and use of this information.
General
This Privacy Statement is governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of New Jersey, without respect to its conflict of laws principles. Jurisdiction for any claims arising under the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement shall lie exclusively with the state and federal courts of the State of New Jersey. If any provision of this Privacy Statement is found to be invalid by a court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of this Privacy Statement, which shall remain in full force and effect.
DMD Healthcare Communications NetworkSM Privacy Statement
This digital service participates in the DMD Healthcare Communication NetworkSM (the “Network”), and as such has implemented various technologies for universal registration/login among all Network member websites. These technologies are managed by DMD Marketing Corp. (“DMD”), and may involve the collection, receipt, and sharing of information with DMD, its clients and other Network members. If you would like to understand how this digital service’s participation in the Network affects your privacy, please click here:
http://usersupport.dmdconnects.com/PrivacyPolicy.htm
Please note that the Network registration/login system may be different from the registration/login used by this digital service for other products and services. To the extent that anything in this privacy policy conflicts with the policy for the Network technologies, the conflict will be resolved in favor of the policy applicable to the Network technologies.
Privacy Statement last updated, September, 2017.
Eliminate Complexity in Treating Type 2 Diabetes
Do you need help in deciding which treatment option is best for your patients?
Get the Free Software
Advertisement
eNewsletter Sign Up
Don't miss a thing!
Sign Up for Diabetes In Control eNewsletters!
Exenatide (Bydureon)
Exenatide (Byetta)
Glimepiride
Glipizide (Glucotrol)
Glipizide (Glucotrol XL)
Insulin Aspart
Insulin Detemir
Insulin Glargine
Insulin Human
Insulin Human & Protamine (Humulin N)
Insulin Human & Protamine (Novolin N)
Repaglinide (Prandin)
Repaglinide (Prandin)
© Copyright 2020 DiabetesInControl.com, All Rights Reserved.
